

RADIANT C. JUAN

Full Stack Web Developer

4209 QUE BALAG STREET, BARANGAY UGONG VALENZUELA CITY, PH, 1440

- (+63) 9055629640
- 🔀 radiantcjuan@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/radiant-juan-2b495391
- https://github.com/radiantjuan
- https://radiantcjuan.me

SKILLS

In my 8 years of experience as a Web Developer, I have the necessary skill set and knowledge to help your company to be profitable. My mission is to deliver operational excellence, productivity, and compliance to ensure and maximize client services, minimize costs they serve and most importantly drive revenue for their business.

Coding

Scripting

Laravel CakePHP Drupal Wordpress

Database

MongoDB MySQL MSSQL FireBase JavaScript jQuery

React JS Ionic with React Backbone.js

CSS

CSS3 Bootstrap Sass Less

Cloud Administration and Analytics

AWS Digital Ocean Apache Nginx Cpanel Plesk Kibana DataDog Tealium

Google Tag Manager Google Analytics

Project Management Tools

AGILE Scrum with combination of: CI/CD Kanban TDD

Atlassian Products

Operating Systems

Linux, Mac, Windows

Repositories and Versioning

Git, BitBucket, GitHub, GitLab

EXPERIENCE

Temple and Webster (Diversify 00S)

Position: Full-Stack Engineer Location: Sydney, Australia

Duration: JANUARY 25, 2021 - PRESENT

Temple and webster's product is an online store that sells, home, kitchen, and office tools and furnitures, more like an IKEA but online, the company is based in Sydney Australia, I work for them remotely with the help of Diversify offshore staffing solutions.

I handle the development, implementation, management, optimization, and continuous improvement of their e-commerce website.

As a team, we also have a strong process and currently using scrum.

Skills: PHP, JavaScript, Scrum, jQuery, CSS, Linux, HTML, Kanban, Apache, Microsoft SQL Server, Extreme Programming, Backbone.js, Git, Web Development

HungryHungry (Microsourcing)

Position: PHP Developer

Location: Melbourne, Australia

Duration: MAY 15, 2017 - JANUARY 22, 2021

Hungryhungry is an online ordering system provider for restaurants in Australia, they have 500+ active clients currently, building an e-commerce website using their web application product with custom CMS called "hungyhungry admin" as one of their services, they also include a tablet application POS system called "HH Hub" where the customers manage online orders. I work for them remotely with the help of MicroSourcing Inc.

My role as a PHP Developer is to develop, implement, manage, optimize and continuous improvement of the Hungryhungry admin, it's a full-stack development using back-end and front-end skills, I also do API development for the "HH Hub", I also do DevOps work but not limited to AWS EC2, RDS, and Cloud formation configuration, and linux.

Skills: PHP, ReactJS, MySQL, JavaScript, Scrum, jQuery, CSS, Linux, HTML, Kanban, Apache, Drupal, Google Tag Manager, Extreme Programming, Git, Web Development, Datadog, Amazon Web Services (AWS)

IBM Solutions Delivery Inc.

Position: Web Applications Developer Location: Quezon City, Philippines Duration: SEPT 2015 - APR 2017

IBM has a subsidiary company called "IBM Solutions Delivery Inc." one of their projects is called Project "Donald" where their client is ABS-CBN one of the famous TV network in the Philippines, I was originally an employee of ABC-CBN and I was transitioned to IBM.

With my role as an Applications Developer, I develop promotional websites from scratch one example is that if they have a movie that they are currently promoting or an album from one of their artists, I was also the sole developer for SkyCable's website which is the number one Cable and broadband provider in the Philippines.

Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Apache, Git, Web Development, CakePHP

Affinity X

Position: Web Developer

Location: Quezon City, Philippines Duration: SEPT 2014 - SEPT 2015

Affinity X is a Marketing and Design Company, My role as a web developer is to create mostly an email marketing, and create website occationally using wordpress, yola, joomla and drupal.

Skills: PHP · CSS · HTML · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · WordPress · Drupal · Web Development

EDUCATION

FEU - Institute of Technology (formerly: FEU - East Asia College), Manila - BS Computer Science Major in Software Engineering

MAY 2010 - APRIL 2014, Nicanor Reyes St., Sampaloc, Manila, Philippines

Accomplishments and applications developed:

• Kaidoku: Japanese character image recognizer and translator Android mobile application

An image processing mobile app that uses Tesseract Optical Character Recognition to recognize Japanese character from a raw image, convert it into a text data and translate the recognized text into English as my latest project.

Health Buff Assistant: health and fitness Android mobile application

Developed using Android Development Tools as a thesis project by doing basic research, which improved my skills and techniques in Android and Java programming and in project managing